【The fate that cannot be liberated】
[해방될 수 없는 운명]
[Episode 15]
[15화]
His brother sacrificed himself and left him with Rong Yu.
그의 형은 자신을 희생 하고 그를 Rong Yu에게 맡겼습니다.
They want you to live a normal life.
그들은 당신이 평범한 삶을 살기를 원합니다.
if i were your family
내가 당신의 가족이라면
I don't want you to get involved again.
나는 당신이 다시 참여하는 것을 원하지 않습니다 .
If you decide to refuse,
거절하기로 결정했다면,
I will understand.
나는 이해할 것이다.
Indeed, I carry a heavy burden.
사실 저는 무거운 짐을 지고 있습니다.
my only burden is
내 유일한 짐은
Why does Your Majesty trust you?
폐하께서는 왜 당신을 신뢰하십니까?
For an ordinary woman like me.
나같은 평범한 여자에겐
Because you are from the He family.
당신은 He 가족 출신이기 때문입니다.
I checked
나는 확인했다
A letter condemning the He family
He 가족을 비난하는 편지
It was forged by Mr. Zhongyong.
Zhongyong 씨가 위조했습니다.
Those who will not betray Jialin
가림을 배반하지 않는 자
It must be the He family.
He 가족임에 틀림없어요.
Only Your Majesty
오직 폐하뿐이십니다
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
Our loyalty.
우리의 충성심.
I will show you
내가 보여줄게
one day.
어느 날.
I never gave up my desire to avenge my family.
나는 가족에게 복수하려는 열망을 결코 포기하지 않았습니다.
His Majesty also said
폐하께서도 말씀하셨다.
I am from the He family.
나는 He 가족 출신입니다.
Since the death of my father and brother,
아버지와 형이 세상을 떠난 이후로
Clean up the responsibilities of the loyal palace
충궁의 책임을 청산하다
Protect the country and His Majesty
나라와 폐하를 보호하십시오
fell on me.
나에게 떨어졌다.
A deposed emperor.
폐위된 황제.
A female general.
여성 장군.
We are affected by our environment. The road ahead is difficult,
우리는 환경의 영향을 받습니다. 앞길이 험난하고,
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
How far can we go together.
우리는 얼마나 멀리 갈 수 있습니까?
I go
나 간다
Do your best.
최선을 다해.
I have nothing to give you
나는 당신에게 줄 것이 아무것도 없습니다
But my father only left me a hundred secret guards.
하지만 아버지는 나에게 비밀 경비병 100명만 남겨 주셨습니다.
You can ship them however you want.
원하는 대로 배송할 수 있습니다.
Some hid in the palace,
일부는 궁전에 숨어 있었고,
Others, outside it.
다른 것들은 그것 밖에 있습니다.
No one knows they exist.
아무도 그들이 존재하는지 모릅니다.
- listen. - Yes.
- 듣다. - 예.
from now on,
지금부터,
The one next to me
내 옆에있는 사람
will be your new owner.
당신의 새로운 주인이 될 것입니다.
her words
그녀의 말
Those are my words.
그게 내 말이다.
- Understood. - Spread out to investigate.
- 이해했다. - 조사를 위해 퍼져라.
Sim.
심.
It was you who killed your father
네 아버지를 죽인 건 너였어
and brothers.
그리고 형제들.
We do not collude with the enemy.
우리는 적과 공모하지 않습니다.
I didn't collude with Xunnan either.
나도 Xunnan과 공모하지 않았습니다.
And Xunnan?
그리고 Xunnan?
I know nothing about Xunnan.
나는 Xunnan에 대해 아무것도 모른다.
Instead of seeking revenge,
복수를 하기보다는,
It would be better if you took your own life.
스스로 목숨을 끊는 것이 더 나을 것입니다.
You are the real culprit.
당신이 진짜 범인입니다.
It was you who caused death
죽음을 초래한 건 바로 너였어
- from your whole family! - shut up.
- 온 가족이요! - 입 다물어.
Jiuling,
지울링,
Nice to meet you.
만나서 반가워요.
What?
무엇?
whenever i miss you
내가 당신을 그리워할 때마다
You show up.
당신이 나타납니다.
That's legal.
그것은 합법적입니다.
Sim.
심.
always
언제나
It will appear when I am sad.
내가 슬플 때 나타납니다.
No.
아니요.
Not sad.
슬프지 않다.
I mean, I miss you.
내 말은, 당신이 그리워요.
it's getting dark.
어두워지고있다.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
I bought you some candies.
나는 당신에게 사탕을 사주었습니다.
And you?
당신은요?
Why are you here alone so late?
왜 이렇게 늦게 혼자 왔나요?
I asked the young master to take me out of the palace to buy some.
나는 젊은 스승에게 나를 궁전 밖으로 데리고 나가서 좀 사달라고 부탁했습니다.
You like it.
당신은 그것을 좋아합니다.
He learned to do things alone.
그는 혼자 일하는 법을 배웠습니다.
Why don't you send them to your house?
당신 집으로 보내지 그래요?
What if you get lost?
길을 잃으면 어떻게 되나요?
How do I get home?
집에 어떻게 가나요?
I won't get lost. I remember the way to the store
나는 길을 잃지 않을 것이다. 가게로 가는 길을 기억해요
and the path to the astrology gallery.
그리고 점성술 갤러리로 가는 길.
And how to pick you up at home.
그리고 집에서 픽업하는 방법.
you know i don't
내가 모르는 거 알잖아
Did I pick you up at home?
내가 집에 데리러 왔어?
We go home.
우리는 집에 간다.
Your Highness.
전하.
We worked hard for several days and nights to get here.
우리는 여기까지 오기 위해 며칠 밤낮을 열심히 일했습니다 .
He had been out for almost six hours.
그는 거의 6시간 동안 밖에 있었습니다.
The wind is very cold.
바람이 매우 차갑습니다.
Please take good care of yourself.
자신을 잘 돌보십시오.
Let's find an inn.
여관을 찾아보자.
The books and pens are here.
책과 펜은 여기 있어요.
Children's foldable turtle
어린이용 접이식 거북이
I gave it to you last time
저번에 줬잖아
Also here.
여기도 있습니다.
everything's ready.
모든 것이 준비되었습니다.
This is a festival.
이것은 축제입니다.
Many shops outside are closed.
밖에 있는 많은 상점들이 문을 닫았습니다.
Why go to an astrology studio?
왜 점성술 스튜디오에 가나요?
This is not a class.
이것은 수업이 아닙니다.
Teachers gather together
선생님들이 한자리에 모여
The homeless young disciples
노숙자 어린 제자들
Study roles they have learned previously.
이전에 배운 역할을 연구합니다 .
In fact,
사실은,
It’s up to the young master whether he goes or not.
갈지 말지는 젊은 주인에게 달려 있습니다.
So, Rong Yu, we don’t want
그래서 Rong Yu, 우리는 원하지 않습니다
Go to an astrology studio.
점성술 스튜디오에 가보세요.
last night,
어젯밤,
The wind blew all night.
밤새도록 바람이 불었습니다.
It's still cloudy now.
지금도 여전히 흐립니다.
It may rain.
비가 올거 같아.
Master. you can barely remember
주인. 당신은 거의 기억하지 못해요
There is nothing in the class.
수업에는 아무것도 없습니다.
We'd better stay home.
집에 있는 게 낫겠다.
No, we have to go.
아니, 우리는 가야 해요.
Master, you have changed. He doesn’t even take advice anymore.
선생님, 달라졌어요. 그는 더 이상 조언도 받아들이지 않습니다.
I want to work harder
더 열심히 하고 싶어요
and learn more about things.
그리고 사물에 대해 더 많이 알아보세요.
This way I can protect you in the future.
이렇게 하면 앞으로도 당신을 보호할 수 있어요.
Jiuling,
지울링,
Not only is it cold outside, it's also dangerous.
밖은 추울 뿐만 아니라 위험하기도 합니다.
Do you know this is dangerous?
이거 위험한 거 아시죠?
Today I will take you to an astrology center.
오늘은 점성술 센터로 여러분을 데려가겠습니다.
let's go.
갑시다.
- You can leave now. - Yes.
- 이제 나가셔도 됩니다. - 예.
At.
에.
Are you going to an astrology clinic?
점성술 클리닉에 가시나요?
Today is a school day.
오늘은 학교 가는 날이에요.
Flatten, be careful , and stay closer to the young master.
평평하게 하고, 조심 하고, 젊은 주인에게 더 가까이 다가가세요.
The capital is unstable.
수도가 불안정합니다.
and.
그리고.
Yu, you can go.
유, 가셔도 돼요.
I want to talk to He Jiuling.
He Jiuling과 이야기하고 싶습니다.
Wait for me in the carriage.
마차에서 나를 기다려주세요.
Today I will take you to an astrology center.
오늘은 점성술 센터로 여러분을 데려가겠습니다 .
you are now
너는 지금
More convincing than me.
나보다 더 설득력이 있다.
I took care of him for many years.
나는 수년 동안 그를 돌보았습니다.
You flatter me.
당신은 나에게 아첨합니다.
I was not flattered.
나는 기분이 좋지 않았습니다.
Whether in the past or now,
옛날이든 지금이든,
Whether he understands it or not,
그 사람이 이해하든 말든,
he often
그는 종종
Be honest with you.
솔직하게 말하세요.
This is quite ironic.
이것은 참으로 아이러니한 일이다.
my Lord.
군주.
yesterday
어제
When you leave the palace
궁궐을 나오면
He came back very late.
그는 매우 늦게 돌아왔습니다.
where did you go?
어디 갔어?
Do you need me to say more?
더 말할 필요가 있나요?
Do
하다
- Is there anything you can't pronounce? - No.
- 발음할 수 없는 게 있나요? - 아니요.
Since there is not,
없기 때문에,
Why should he return the carriage that was supposed to carry her?
왜 그녀를 태우기로 되어 있던 마차를 돌려보내야 합니까?
And send the servants home?
그리고 하인들을 집으로 보내시겠습니까?
He was alone.
그는 혼자였습니다.
In this capital,
이 수도에서는
Place and content
장소와 내용
Can you let me stay late?
늦게까지 머물게 해줄 수 있나요?
I went to see my father.
나는 아버지를 만나러 갔다.
Because, on Lunar New Year’s Eve,
왜냐면 설날에는
I'm home alone.
나는 집에 혼자 있다.
Better go visit my father
아버지를 만나러 가는 게 좋을 것 같아요
my brother and sister-in-law
내 동생과 여동생
And spend the holidays with them.
그리고 그들과 함께 휴일을 보내세요.
Are you exaggerating?
과장하고 있나요?
But you don't have to go alone.
하지만 혼자 갈 필요는 없습니다.
I know you don't like my family
당신이 우리 가족을 좋아하지 않는다는 걸 알아요
I don't want people in the house
집에 사람이 있는 걸 원하지 않아요
Know where I'm going.
내가 어디로 가는지 알아라.
and how it should be
그리고 어떻게되어야합니까?
It's a night of reunion,
재회의 밤이군요
Why do I want everyone to go to the cemetery with me ?
왜 모두가 나와 함께 묘지에 가길 바라나요?
And take the bad luck home with you?
그리고 불운을 집으로 가져가시겠습니까?
So I sent them back.
그래서 나는 그들을 다시 보냈습니다.
If you think my words or actions are inappropriate,
나의 말이나 행동이 부적절하다고 생각된다면 ,
There won't be a next time.
다음에는 없을 것입니다.
You can leave now.
지금 떠나셔도 됩니다.
Yu has been waiting for you for a long time.
유씨는 오랫동안 당신을 기다리고 있었습니다.
【Rongfu】
【롱푸】
- It's cold? - No.
- 추워? - 아니요.
This is very cool.
이것은 매우 멋지다.
Are you on the wagon now?
지금 마차를 타고 있나요?
if you lie to me
당신이 나에게 거짓말을 한다면
I'm not talking to you anymore.
나는 더 이상 당신과 이야기하지 않습니다.
joke.
농담.
know the danger
위험을 알아라
Who mentioned it before?
이전에 누가 언급했나요?
Like if you fell into a lake.
마치 호수에 빠진 것처럼요.
I don't know why he went to the water to catch fish last time.
저번에는 왜 물고기를 잡으러 물에 갔는지 모르겠어요 .
Who told you this nonsense?
누가 이런 말도 안되는 소리를 했나요?
In the future, no matter what others say,
앞으로는 남들이 뭐래도
Don't listen.
듣지 마세요.
you understood?
이해했어?
So tell me.
그러니 나에게 말해봐.
Who else?
그밖에 누가?
Except Rong Ye,
롱 예를 제외하고,
o Zhanping,
오 잔핑,
a Heshan,
허산,
Others are seen as others.
다른 사람들은 다른 사람들처럼 보입니다.
And you?
당신은요?
about me,
나에 대해서,
You shouldn't listen to me either.
너도 내 말을 듣지 말아야 해.
in fact
사실은
I'm a liar.
나는 거짓말쟁이입니다.
Like I'm lying now.
내가 지금 거짓말을 하고 있는 것처럼요.
Not the future,
미래가 아닌,
I will tell you a lot of lies.
나는 당신에게 많은 거짓말을 할 것입니다.
You are different from others.
당신은 다른 사람들과 다릅니다.
You don't look like
당신은 닮지 않은 것 같아요
So does my uncle.
내 삼촌도 마찬가지야.
what is the difference?
차이점은 무엇입니까?
A
ㅏ
the difference
차이점
This is
이것은
you are mine.
당신은 내 것입니다.
Rong Yu, who did you learn this from?
유영 씨, 누구한테 배웠어요?
But did you learn it at the Astrology Pavilion?
그런데 점성술관에서 배웠나요?
Are you spying on others reading?
다른 사람들이 읽는 것을 감시하고 있습니까?
selenium
셀렌
Your facial expression may be a little more angry
좀 더 화난 표정일지도
There is more evil
악이 더 많다
Probably not that funny.
아마도 그다지 재미없을 것입니다.
I won't be angry with you.
나는 당신에게 화를 내지 않을 것입니다.
I won't be mean to you either.
나도 당신에게 못되게 굴지는 않을 거예요.
I'm yours too.
나도 당신 것입니다.
I'm yours.
나는 당신 것입니다.
So from now on I will only listen to you.
그러니까 앞으로는 당신 말만 듣겠습니다.
Is he okay?
그 사람 괜찮아요?
Your Majesty, we have arrived.
폐하, 도착했습니다.
Miledy.
마일디.
Milady, why are you blushing?
밀레디, 왜 얼굴이 빨개지나요?
It must be because the cabin is stuffy.
아무래도 객실이 답답해서 그런 것 같아요.
Was it very stuffy there at that time?
그때 그곳이 많이 답답했나요?
My face was frozen.
내 얼굴이 얼었다.
So why don't you come in?
그럼 들어오지 그래?
I can go.
나는 갈 수있다.
I can still walk a little.
아직은 조금 걸을 수 있어요.
Meet my friend Wu Ritan.
내 친구 Wu Ritan을 만나보세요.
It's raining. It's raining.
비가 온다. 비가 온다.
Quickly!
빠르게!
It's raining.
비가 온다.
Zhangping
장핑
Zhanping!
잔핑!
Master.
주인.
It's raining.
비가 온다.
Yes, Master, the lady said it's going to rain, and it's raining hard.
네, 스승님, 아주머니가 비가 올 거라고 했는데, 비가 많이 온다더군요.
Could it be that after spending so long with the young master?
젊은 스승과 오랜 시간을 보낸 뒤에도 그럴 수 있을까 ?
Has she also learned to predict the future?
그녀는 미래를 예측하는 법도 배웠나요?
- How can I. - Umbrella!
- 내가 어떻게 할 수있는. - 우산!
I know, young boss.
알아요, 젊은 상사님.
When you finish writing the characters,
캐릭터 작성을 마치면 ,
If it's still raining, I'll get an umbrella.
아직도 비가 오면 우산을 가져올게요.
Jiuling didn't bring an umbrella.
Jiuling은 우산을 가져오지 않았습니다.
correct.
옳은.
You didn't take an umbrella with you when you left.
당신은 떠날 때 우산을 가지고 가지 않았습니다.
- Fortunately, it didn't rain heavily. - I'll ask someone to bring it.
- 다행히 큰 비는 내리지 않았습니다. - 다른 사람한테 가져오라고 할게요.
Master, wait for me.
선생님, 기다려주세요.
I know
알아요
About what happened in Xunnan
Xunnan에서 일어난 일에 대해
You have no choice.
너는 선택의 여지가 없어.
Even if you want to save me
날 구하고 싶어도
Can't change the outcome.
결과를 바꿀 수는 없습니다.
Even though I'm a king now,
지금은 왕이 되어도
and has a high status,
지위도 높고,
all
모두
You can't go back.
당신은 돌아갈 수 없습니다.
This time I came to Jialin
이번에 Jialin에 왔습니다.
To save his father and brothers.
아버지와 형제들을 구하기 위해.
But I didn't expect that.
하지만 나는 그것을 기대하지 않았습니다.
Ling, the only thing I can do now is
링, 내가 지금 할 수 있는 건 그것뿐이야
I just want to take you away.
나는 단지 당신을 데려가고 싶습니다.
Although?
하지만?
I can help you get revenge.
나는 당신이 복수할 수 있도록 도와줄 수 있어요.
I can give you anything you want.
당신이 원하는 것은 무엇이든 줄 수 있어요.
If you want to play freely in the bamboo forest,
대나무숲에서 자유롭게 놀고 싶다면,
random.
무작위의.
If you want to bully you again
또 괴롭히고 싶으면
In Xunnan, I will protect you,
Xunnan에서 내가 당신을 보호하겠습니다.
No one dares to hurt him again.
누구도 감히 그를 다치게 할 수 없습니다.
There is such a depressing place
이렇게 우울한 곳이 있구나
And such a marriage,
그리고 그런 결혼,
i don't want you
나는 당신을 원하지 않는다
Continue for another day.
다른 날에도 계속하세요.
Teacher Rong has done a lot for you.
Rong 선생님은 당신을 위해 많은 일을 해주셨습니다.
I will find a way to cure him.
나는 그를 치료할 방법을 찾을 것입니다.
Will you follow me to Xunnan?
나를 따라 Xunnan으로 갈 것인가?
Why do you hesitate?
왜 망설이나요?
Miledy. it hurts. it hurts.
마일디. 아파요. 아파요.
looking at you. She is already an adult
너를보고있는. 그녀는 이미 어른이다
And just know how to play.
그리고 노는 방법만 알면 됩니다.
But isn’t it a holiday?
그런데 휴일이 아니지 않나?
Why don't you leave me alone? stop complaining.
나를 내버려두는 게 어때요? 불평 좀 그만해.
Are you annoyed by my complaints? I'm going to beat you.
내 불평 때문에 짜증났나요? 나는 당신을 이길 것입니다.
This is a holiday.
이것은 휴일입니다.
I'm very happy. You're happy too, right?
나는 매우 행복 해요. 당신도 행복해요, 그렇죠?
When you see Yuhan, don’t tell her
유한이 만나면 말하지 마세요
It means you are not sleeping at home.
집에서 잠을 자지 않는다는 뜻이다.
She doesn't care. I do not care.
그녀는 상관하지 않습니다. 난 상관 없어.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Yuhan told me she was fine.
유한은 괜찮다고 말했어요.
I didn't expect that she would have a lover now.
이제 그녀에게 애인이 생길 줄 은 몰랐습니다 .
The man in dark clothes
어두운 옷을 입은 남자
This is definitely not Rong Yu.
이것은 확실히 Rong Yu가 아닙니다.
They just stood there talking.
그들은 단지 거기 서서 이야기를 하고 있을 뿐이었습니다.
How did he become a lover?
그는 어떻게 연인이 되었나요?
Why don't you stay with me?
나와 함께 지내는 게 어때?
Let's take a look.
한 번 보자.
Why do you hesitate?
왜 망설이나요?
Don't go, sister.
가지 마세요, 언니.
Silta. he.
실타. 그.
No, it’s Mrs. Rong!
아니요, 롱 부인이에요!
How strange to see you! My brother and I came over to say hello.
당신을 보니 정말 이상하네요! 저와 동생이 인사를 하러 왔습니다.
Who is this?
누구세요?
you do not need to know.
넌 알 필요 없어.
how long.
얼마나 오래.
You still here
당신 아직 여기 있군요
This is very rude.
이것은 매우 무례한 일입니다.
Not long ago, you experienced a great disaster.
얼마 전 당신은 큰 재난을 겪었습니다.
But she doesn’t teach you how to be a human being.
하지만 그녀는 인간이 되는 법을 가르쳐주지 않습니다.
You've crossed a line, sister.
선을 넘었어요, 언니.
- You dare to hit me? - No.
- 감히 나를 때릴 셈이냐? - 아니요.
It seems so.
그런 것 같습니다.
criminal's daughter
범죄자의 딸
He has not learned to be cautious and is arrogant.
그는 조심하는 법을 배우지 못했고 오만했습니다.
i need to know today
오늘은 알아야겠어
Who is this guy.
이 사람이 누구입니까.
Who is so blind?
누가 그렇게 눈이 멀었나?
- Jiuling, I bought you an umbrella. - Yu Rong,
- Jiuling, 내가 우산을 사줬어요. - 유롱,
It's not raining now.
지금은 비가 내리지 않습니다.
correct.
옳은.
Master Rong.
롱 선생님.
Master, when I parked the carriage,
선생님, 제가 마차를 주차했을 때,
I throw mud at you
나는 당신에게 진흙을 던집니다
with mud.
진흙으로.
what can we do?
우리는 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
May I ask the owner of Xingxiang Pavilion?
Xingxiang Pavilion의 주인에게 물어봐도 될까요 ?
compensation?
보상?
Well, I'm not going to make it up to you.
글쎄, 나는 당신에게 그것을 보상하지 않을 것입니다.
you.
너.
One piece of clothing is no big deal.
옷 한 벌은 별 문제가 되지 않습니다.
But Mr. Rong, your wife will meet a man on the street.
그런데 롱 씨, 당신의 아내는 길거리에서 남자를 만날 것입니다.
I think this is a big problem.
나는 이것이 큰 문제라고 생각한다.
Why are you looking at me?
왜 나를보고있어?
You are a man.
당신은 남자입니다.
What?
무엇?
Your voice is too loud.
목소리가 너무 큽니다.
Your voice is deep.
당신의 목소리는 깊습니다.
He is a real man.
그는 진짜 남자입니다.
Sorry, I didn't recognize you.
죄송합니다. 인식하지 못했습니다.
Rong Yu, what are you talking about?
롱 유, 무슨 소리 야?
And you, why are you laughing?
그런데 당신은 왜 웃고 있나요?
Do que chamou a Rong Yu?
que chamou가 Rong Yu인가요?
What?
무엇?
A fact known to everyone in the capital
수도에 있는 모두가 알고 있는 사실
What can't be said?
말할 수 없는 것은 무엇입니까?
Fool.
바보.
You married a stupid man.
당신은 멍청한 남자와 결혼했습니다.
-Jiu Ling. - I'm acting.
-지우 링. - 연기 중이에요.
Ling, stop fighting.
링, 그만 싸우세요.
how long,
얼마나 오래,
Multiple sclerosis. Jiang
다발성 경화증. 지앙
Still so ineffective.
여전히 너무 비효율적입니다.
Do you dare to hurt me?
감히 나에게 상처를 줄 수 있어?
She is hurt.
그녀는 다쳤습니다.
It's best to see a doctor.
의사를 만나는 것이 가장 좋습니다.
Quickly.
빠르게.
Why did you mess with her?
왜 그녀를 엉망으로 만들었나요?
- I'll tell you something. -Ling,
- 내가 하나 말해줄게. -링,
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
잘 지내요. 괜찮아요.
Who are you?
누구세요?
he is
그는
My big brother.
내 큰 형.
Don't you need to go back to Xingxiang Pavilion?
Xingxiang Pavilion 으로 돌아갈 필요가 없나요 ?
And you?
당신은요?
My brother and I need to talk.
형이랑 얘기 좀 해야 해요.
I will wait for you.
나는 당신을 기다릴 것입니다.
today,
오늘,
Don’t you need to go to the Astrology Pavilion to practice calligraphy?
서예를 연습하려면 점성술관 에 갈 필요가 없나요 ?
I asked for leave from the teacher.
선생님께 휴학을 요청했어요.
Then I'll send her back first.
그럼 내가 먼저 그녀를 돌려보낼게요.
I will go with you.
나는 당신과 함께 갈 것입니다.
[Turn around in the tavern]
[주점에서 돌아서다]
Have you got a meal yet?
식사는 아직 안 하셨나요?
not yet.
아직 아님.
I'll bring you something to eat.
먹을 것 좀 가져다 드릴게요.
What do you want to eat?
너 뭐 먹고 싶니?
You know I'm not picky.
내가 까다롭지 않다는 거 알잖아요.
I'll prepare something fresh for you.
당신을 위해 신선한 것을 준비하겠습니다.
I haven't eaten yet.
나는 아직 먹지 않았습니다.
I haven't finished eating yet
아직 식사가 끝나지 않았어
Is there gold thread ramen this morning?
오늘 아침에는 금실라면이 있나요?
Zhanping wants you to eat eggs, but you can't.
Zhanping은 계란을 먹고 싶어 하지만 그럴 수 없습니다.
Why haven't you eaten yet?
왜 아직 먹지 않았나요?
I didn't have lunch.
나는 점심을 먹지 않았다.
what time is it?
지금 몇 시지?
Then everything is fine.
그러면 모든 것이 괜찮습니다.
What do you want to eat?
너 뭐 먹고 싶니?
- I have no idea. - you do not know?
- 모르겠어요. - 넌 몰라?
Rong Yu, are you really hungry?
롱유 씨, 정말 배고프세요?
correct. I believe I have desires.
옳은. 나는 나에게 욕망이 있다고 믿는다.
I'm going to buy some snacks.
나는 간식을 좀 사려고 해요.
do you remember me?
나를 기억해요?
It seems he doesn't remember at all.
그는 전혀 기억하지 못하는 것 같습니다.
you are no longer
당신은 더 이상 없습니다
The best young master in Jialin.
Jialin 최고의 젊은 스승.
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
What makes you who you are today.
오늘날의 당신을 만드는 것은 무엇입니까?
Theoretically
이론적으로는
You shouldn't be like this.
당신은 이렇게해서는 안됩니다.
It seems that Ling and I both owe you one.
링과 나 둘 다 당신에게 빚을 진 것 같군요.
You helped her.
당신은 그녀를 도왔습니다.
Saved her life.
그녀의 생명을 구했습니다.
I thank
감사합니다
Replace the wine with a cup of tea.
와인을 차 한잔으로 바꿔보세요.
Whether we thank you or owe you,
우리가 당신에게 감사하든 빚을 지고 있든,
We can't use Ling's life to repay.
우리는 링의 삶을 갚기 위해 사용할 수 없습니다.
what do you want? supreme status,
당신은 무엇을 원하세요? 최고 지위,
get rich
부자가 되다
Or something else?
또는 다른 것?
I can even promise
약속할 수도 있어요
to cure it.
그것을 치료하기 위해.
Master, do you understand what I mean?
선생님, 무슨 말인지 아시겠어요?
If you don't understand, that's okay.
이해하지 못하더라도 괜찮습니다.
No consent is required.
동의가 필요하지 않습니다.
Who are you?
누구세요?
who I am?
나는 누구입니까?
If I need to say anything
내가 무슨 말을 해야 한다면
consider me
나를 고려
Someone who will steal your wife.
당신의 아내를 훔칠 사람.
let me see.
좀 보자.
No.
아니요.
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
Why is water splashing everywhere?
왜 물이 여기저기서 튀는 걸까요?
Why are your hands red?
손이 왜 빨개요?
Burned?
불탔나요?
Boss, bring me a basin of ice water!
사장님, 얼음물 한 대야를 가져다주세요!
- It's coming. - Flatten!
- 그것은오고. - 평평하게!
Zhanping, come here quickly.
잔핑, 빨리 이리로 와라.
The tea is a little hot. everything will get better.
차는 조금 뜨겁습니다. 모든 것이 좋아질 것입니다.
It might be nothing to others.
다른 사람에게는 아무것도 아닐 수도 있습니다.
His frail body may have been scarred.
그의 연약한 몸에 상처가 있었을 수도 있습니다.
let me see.
좀 보자.
Have you ever been in a war?
전쟁에 참여해 본 적이 있나요?
Do you think we can fight?
우리가 싸울 수 있을 것 같아?
Indeed, sometimes
실제로 때로는
He has a bit of a temper, like a child.
그 사람은 어린아이처럼 약간의 성질을 갖고 있어요 .
Ignore him.
그를 무시해.
I don't plan to.
나는 그럴 계획이 없습니다.
What's there?
거기 무엇이 있나요?
The young master was burned to death.
젊은 주인은 불에 타 죽었습니다.
Big book.
큰 책.
First I cool it with ice water.
먼저 얼음물로 식혀줍니다.
- Go back and apply cooling ointment. - correct.
- 돌아가서 냉각 연고를 바르십시오. - 옳은.
Zhan Ping, take the young master home.
잔핑, 젊은 스승을 집으로 데려가세요.
No.
아니요.
If you don't go home and apply ointment
집에 가서 연고를 바르지 않으면
You will be unable to sleep at night because of the pain.
통증 때문에 밤에 잠을 이루지 못할 것입니다.
If you go there, I'll go too.
당신이 거기 가면 나도 갈게요.
I'll be back soon.
곧 돌아올거야.
So I will come back later as well.
그러니 저도 나중에 다시 오겠습니다.
Rong Yu, you said you would listen to me.
유용씨, 당신은 내 말을 들어주겠다고 했지요.
European Union...
유럽 ​​연합...
You don't know how to take care of yourself,
당신은 자신을 돌보는 방법을 모릅니다.
I do not blame you. I ask you to come back and give me medicine,
나는 당신을 비난하지 않습니다. 다시 오셔서 약을 달라고 하세요.
This is for your own good.
이것은 당신 자신의 이익을 위한 것입니다.
You don't listen either.
당신도 듣지 않습니다.
Zhan Ping, take the young master back.
잔핑, 젊은 스승을 다시 데려가세요.
Master, let’s go back first.
선생님, 먼저 돌아가세요.
Look, the lady is already angry.
보세요, 그 여자는 이미 화가 났어요.
Come, Your Majesty.
오세요, 폐하.
My lady will be back soon.
아가씨는 곧 돌아올 거예요.
- Even? - Clear.
- 심지어? - 분명한.
let's go.
갑시다.
Do you really want to come back later?
나중에 정말 다시 오시겠어요?
You didn't lie, did you?
당신은 거짓말을 하지 않았죠?
I won't lie to you.
나는 당신에게 거짓말을하지 않을 것입니다.
But you said in the carriage
하지만 당신은 마차에서 말했어요
You are a liar.
넌 거짓말 쟁이 야.
- I... - I'm waiting for you at home.
- 난... - 집에서 기다리고 있어요.
I only listen to you.
나는 당신의 말만 듣습니다.
Can you stop lying?
거짓말을 그만둘 수 있나요?
he's good.
그는 좋아.
Come on, Master.
자, 마스터.
Master, let's go.
선생님, 가세요.
let's go.
갑시다.
Come on, Master.
자, 마스터.
It is said that when Mr. Song was in trouble,
송씨가 곤경에 처했을 때 ,
Someone forced Master Song's sedan to stop.
누군가가 송 사부의 세단을 강제 로 멈추게 했습니다.
But we don't know who.
하지만 우리는 누구인지 모릅니다.
The drug that caused Mr. Song’s driver to fall into coma
송씨 운전기사를 혼수상태에 빠뜨린 약물
From the imperial concubine.
황실 첩에서.
Only used in the palace.
궁에서만 사용됩니다.
This is not something ordinary people can achieve.
이는 보통 사람이 이룰 수 있는 것이 아니다.
People who can get this medicine
이 약을 구할 수 있는 사람
Must be someone from the court.
법원에서 나온 사람이어야 합니다.
Who has close ties to the royal family.
왕실과 긴밀한 관계를 맺고 있는 사람.
Revenge on New Year's Eve.
새해 전날의 복수.
Who has a grudge against him?
그에게 원한을 품은 사람이 누구입니까?
Who is the biggest suspect?
가장 큰 용의자는 누구입니까?
The biggest suspect
가장 큰 용의자
He must be an orphan from the He family.
그는 He 가족의 고아임에 틀림없습니다.
Now, Lord Rong
자, 롱 경
They even sent someone to notify me.
그들은 심지어 나에게 알리기 위해 사람을 보냈습니다.
He Jiuling went to the cake shop
He Jiuling은 케이크 가게에 갔다
That night in the west of the city
그날 밤 도시 서쪽에서
Go buy candy.
가서 사탕을 사세요.
They have witnesses and physical evidence.
그들은 증인과 물리적 증거를 가지고 있습니다.
The young master can also confirm this.
젊은 스승님도 이를 확인할 수 있습니다.
Although,
하지만,
if she leaves the palace
그녀가 궁전을 떠나면
Go west and east of the city
도시의 서쪽과 동쪽으로 이동
Kill the Song Lord
노래왕을 죽여라
Then return to Rongfu
그런 다음 Rongfu로 돌아갑니다.
I don't think she had enough time.
내 생각엔 그녀에게 시간이 충분하지 않은 것 같아.
A girl from the He family
He 가족의 소녀
Can't cause problems.
문제를 일으킬 수 없습니다.
Her whole family died.
그녀의 가족은 모두 죽었습니다.
No one wants to help her.
아무도 그녀를 돕고 싶어하지 않습니다.
- Let's go to the Ministry of Justice. - let's go.
- 법무부로 갑시다. - 갑시다.
Father I...
아버지 나...
group.
그룹.
Are you tired?
너 피곤하니?
Sim.
심.
This depends largely on you.
이것은 주로 당신에게 달려 있습니다.
between me and him,
나와 그 사람 사이,
It's like a knot that can't be untied.
풀리지 않는 매듭과 같습니다.
Pai County,
파이 카운티,
my brothers
내 형제
My sister-in-law died too.
내 여동생도 죽었어.
if it weren't for him
그 사람이 아니었다면
Maybe I can't handle it.
어쩌면 나는 그것을 처리할 수 없습니다.
we must look forward
우리는 기대해야 해
Because there is light on the road ahead.
왜냐하면 앞길에 빛이 있기 때문입니다.
But what if the road ahead
하지만 앞으로 길이 있다면 어떨까요?
Is this a darker abyss?
이것은 더 어두운 심연인가?
Do you still have the courage to move on?
아직도 나아갈 용기가 있나요?
Because of Rong Yu.
롱유 때문이다.
He's here.
그는 여기에 있습니다.
need me.
내가 필요해.
Believe me.
나를 믿어.
it makes me feel
그것은 나를 느끼게 만든다
There is still light in life.
인생에는 아직 빛이 있습니다.
elder brother,
형,
You want me to go with you.
당신은 내가 당신과 함께 가기를 원합니다.
I can not.
나는 할 수 없다.
Is it because of him?
그 사람 때문인가요?
Sim.
심.
Not really.
설마.
You said I could be like before
당신은 내가 예전처럼 될 수 있다고 말했어요
and do whatever you want.
그리고 당신이 원하는 것은 무엇이든 할 수 있습니다.
But Wuhuashan’s sister
하지만 Wuhuashan의 여동생은
and the bullies in the capital
그리고 수도의 불량배들
You can't live the way you used to.
예전처럼 살 수는 없습니다.
I repay Rong Yu.
유용준에게 보답합니다.
As for deep hatred,
깊은 증오에 관해서는,
I need revenge.
복수가 필요해요.
The He family was attacked and beheaded.
He 가족은 공격을 받고 참수당했습니다.
I don't know who that is.
나는 그 사람이 누구인지 모릅니다.
But if you want to stay here alone and take revenge
하지만 여기에 혼자 남아 복수하고 싶다면
Do you think you can really do it?
정말 할 수 있을 것 같나요?
I am.
그래요.
Really,
정말,
Now in Nanjiang,
지금 난장에서는
you have been known
당신은 알려졌습니다
General Zuo.
주오 장군.
but in my heart
하지만 내 마음속에는
You will always be my little sister
당신은 항상 내 여동생이 될 것입니다
No one knows anything
아무도 아무것도 몰라
And protected by Master and me.
그리고 스승님과 제가 보호해 주었습니다.
Who doesn’t want to be a little sister?
누가 여동생이 되고 싶지 않겠어요?
No one knows anything
아무도 아무것도 몰라
And protected by the master and you?
그리고 주인과 당신의 보호를 받습니까?
I have no expectations
나는 기대가 없다
one day
어느 날
I have to find another way out
다른 탈출구를 찾아야 해요
where i was born
내가 태어난 곳
I was raised that way.
나는 그렇게 자랐습니다.
I always thought
나는 항상 생각했다
I will always be that person
나는 언제나 그런 사람이 될 것이다
Ignorant little girl.
무지한 어린 소녀.
If you have already made a decision,
이미 결정을 내리셨다면,
I respect her.
나는 그녀를 존경합니다.
If one day you are tired
어느 날 당신이 피곤하다면
I will help you.
내가 당신을 도울 것입니다.
Master Danrong
마스터 단롱
is a noble master
고귀한 스승이다
Born with a silver spoon in his mouth.
은수저를 입에 물고 태어났다.
he will never be the same again
그는 다시는 예전과 같지 않을 것이다
Just like you and me.
당신과 나처럼.
he can only be
그는 그럴 수 밖에 없어
His weakness on the road to revenge.
복수의 길에서 그의 약점.
I see.
알겠어요.
all good.
문제 없다.
I will wait for good news in Xunnan.
Xunnan에서 좋은 소식을 기다리겠습니다.
next time you miss me
다음에 네가 나를 그리워할 때
I'll go right away.
바로 갈게요.
leave you here alone
당신을 여기 혼자 남겨두세요
here.
여기.
before leaving,
떠나기 전에,
I'll keep a very skilled maid
나는 매우 숙련된 하녀를 두겠다
To protect you.
당신을 보호하기 위해.
I don't need anyone to protect me.
나를 보호해 줄 사람은 필요하지 않습니다.
Let me do this for you.
내가 당신을 위해 이것을 하도록 할게요.
when you want to write to me
네가 나한테 편지를 쓰고 싶을 때
Give it directly to her.
그녀에게 직접 주세요.
It's safer than giving it to someone else.
다른 사람에게 주는 것보다 안전합니다.
correct.
옳은.
You asked me about amnesia fans
기억상실증 팬에 대해 물어보셨어요
When I was in Nanjiang.
내가 난장(南江)에 있을 때였다.
I'm under house arrest
나는 가택연금 중이에요
I didn't get a chance to respond.
나는 대답할 기회를 얻지 못했다.
The little bug you put in the medicine
당신이 약에 넣은 작은 벌레
can be suppressed
억제할 수 있다
Venom activity.
독 활동.
But he also slowly
하지만 그 사람도 천천히
Damage to organs.
장기 손상.
I'm trying to come up with a solution.
나는 해결책을 찾으려고 노력하고 있습니다.
I don't know if it will work.
그것이 효과가 있을지 모르겠습니다.
♫ It’s when the sun sets in the evening♫
♫ 저녁에 해가 지는 때죠♫
♫I have traveled thousands of miles ♫
♫나는 수천 마일을 여행했어요 ♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 달빛 아래서 시타르를 연주해 보세요 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 술은 내가 잊지 못하게 해줄 거예요 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있습니다♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 당신은 조용히 돌아서서 결혼식 장부를 덮습니다♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있습니다♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫I play the sitar softly waiting for someone like you♫
♫나는 너 같은 사람을 기다리며 조용히 시타르를 연주한다 ♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫결국 당신은 나의 피할 수 없는 운명♫